[{"answer": "How we doing", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Am I late", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Am I late", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " What's the point", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You want me to show up late a few nights", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "This isn't the Pine Tree Inn on Route 81, my friend", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " Fuck him.  Great.  Terrific.  Fuck him", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "They tried to electrocute me, my friend", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "It was no fucking accident, my friend. The little one ..", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "So do I", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "No, you gotta go 'cause if you don't get up there every couple weeks you feel guilty. I won't feel guilty, so I don't gotta go", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "We gotta go, my friend", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "This time you gotta go", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "No, you gotta go 'cause if you don't get up there every couple weeks you feel guilty. I won't feel guilty, so I don't gotta go", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I don't gotta go", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "This time you gotta go", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You gotta go", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You bring trunks, my friend", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Swimming trunks", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " my friend paid you off last night, didn't he", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "The hell you don't", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "It wasn't like that", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "No", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Hey pal, I got a mortgage, all right? I got two kids. I got a wife. Besides, he made the deal. There's no shame in it", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yeah, that's how I see it", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "That's what we agreed", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I'm not unhappy", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You, my friend.  All these years you been telling me we're different.  We got novelty, my friend. No one can touch us", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "It never was", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " Just like that, huh?  You're not even gonna give me a chance", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "How should I take it", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "So if I'm so 'late how come you're still here", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "So run a little longer", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "What I mean is", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "So work with me, not against me. Okay", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Is that what you used to do", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "What are they", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Ivory", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Older than me", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": " A seven", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I wear a seven", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "All right, but make it quick.  Shoes!  What size do you wear", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Nine", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": " Nine", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Nine", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "You should've brought a leash, Mr. my friend. The doctor doesn't like to be bitten", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "They never do, Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "What's our friend's problem", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Start him out on cottage cheese. If you've got him on kibble, just soak it a few minutes.  Go down like pudding through a hot pipe", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "No bones", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Yeah.  Something", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "You wanna get a drink", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Regular hours are eight to five", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "You can check in on him tomorrow. Between eight and five", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "my friend, you fellas've made a lot of noise.  What's with the stars", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Virgins", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": " And how about this air? I'm telling you, a few days in this place'll put five years on your life", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Of course it smells like fish. We're on the ocean. What'd you expect, Chanel number five", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Smells like fish", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": " Smells like tuna number two to me", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "Hey, we're connected", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "Great", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "Pearls.  White gown.  Beautiful", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "A few bars", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "They must've bought the same map we did", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "I don't believe it.  You're a romantic, my friend", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "I figure that way we won't get confused", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "Unless you want the right", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Right", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "No, you take the right", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "So you're gonna leave it on. Every night.  For a week", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "Why would I mind", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "Then I'm afraid I don't understand", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "Is that important", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "Accommodate?  I don't think I know what you mean", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "Why don't we let Mr. my friend tell us what he's trying to say", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "Huh", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "Oh. Yeah.  I gotta bunch of them", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": " Hal", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "Two hours ago", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "You're not going to drive", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "It's our goddamn car", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "Nothing", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "I'm not upset", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "What's that supposed to mean", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "You were good", "qsentId": 90}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 93, "question": "Friend", "qsentId": 92}, {"answer": "Must've been a cheap date", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 95, "question": "Soap", "qsentId": 94}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 97, "question": "I told you, my friend.  It's a telethon. No one gets a cent", "qsentId": 96}, {"answer": "What disease", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 99, "question": "You don't know", "qsentId": 98}, {"answer": " What channels it on", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 101, "question": "Sevent", "qsentId": 100}, {"answer": "What do you say we go for a walk, pal", "docId": "Fabulous-Baker-Boys_-The.txt", "asentId": 103, "question": "Come on, friend.  I can smell it on you. Get yourself a cup of coffee.  You'll forget what you're angry about", "qsentId": 102}]